Today we will learn how to put small penis humiliation, or SPH for short, into
practice. A
domination fetish where a man is subjected to comments and gestures about the inadequate
size of his penis and because of his subsequent inability to please a woman, which implies
his worthlessness as a man. Put into practice.
Here are some examples of things to do with a client who is looking for this type
of domination. Now this would be a good time to pause the video and take a photo
on your phone or screen shot to add to your notes.
This can be used as a reference for when you get a client come online who would like
to try SPH. Some examples of things for him to do are make him measure it
with a ruler or hold up your little finger to the screen and tell him how little
it is. Hopefully these examples will give you some ideas and you can continue to
add your own to the list so that you never run out of ideas to do when put on the
spot. You can measure it against small objects, compare it against pictures of real
men, use your pinky finger to hold up to the screen and compare sizes, use your thumb
and forefinger to show him the size of his penis, wank using only two fingers because
it's that tiny, make him measure it with a ruler, say you're going to tell your friends
that you've seen the smallest cock, point and laugh at it, hold up the loser sign
to him, ask him to describe his cock to you, make him rub ice in it to make it smaller,
make him wear women's underwear, make him tell you how pathetic it is.
Things to say. Here are some examples of things to say.
Pause this video now to read through and take notes down once again.
If you find yourself running out of ideas, then laughing a lot and doing the loser
sign can be a good filler while you read through your notes to find something new
to say to your client. Oh it's so cute like a little boy's dick.
I feel sorry for you. I have seen bigger clits to be honest.
Maybe we should just cuddle for a bit instead.
I only want to fuck men with at least 9 inch cocks.
You know there's an operation. You should draw a smiley face on it.
The last guy I slept with was at least 4 inches longer.
How lovely, you brought a scented stick for me.
This explains your expensive car. Is that it?
Oh lovely, I really needed a toothpick. I never knew it could be that small.
What did God punish you for? I heard that excessive masturbation shortens the penis.
Oh look, it's hiding. Don't be shy. Are you cold?
Does it run in the family? Were you castrated?
Deep throat? Honey, it wouldn't even reach my tonsils.
Can I hang my coat on this? Look, my Barbie clothes would fit perfectly.
Here are some examples of things to call it.
Again, please pause now and take your own notes for future reference.
The performance. Be confident. Be confident.
At first you might feel awkward, but most clients who are into this kink don't want
you to hold back and they want you to enjoy saying the nastiest, most hurtful, degrading
things you can think of. Tell your friends.
A lot of small penis humiliation clients enjoy the idea of you mocking the size of
his penis to your friends. Be sure to check if they would like it first, and then
if they agree, you can text or pretend to text your friends making fun of it.
Some even want you to send pictures to your friends.
Laugh at them a lot. Actively laughing at someone's manhood is probably the ultimate
humiliation for them. Don't hold back. A lot of time the humiliation can genuinely
make you giggle, and the client will want to see that.
Have fun with it. Some clients that come on don't even have a small penis, but just
go along with it as if they do. Tell them they aren't worthy of being a man in your
eyes. A man's penis is his most prized possession, and what he is most proud of.
So when it comes to breaking a submissive, the first port of call would be to insult
the length. I hope that you've learned a lot in this video.
Earlier on I asked you to pause the video and take a photo or a screenshot of the
different things that you can do with your client.
You can either do this, or you can write them down in a notepad.
I've spoken about this before on other videos.
I think it's really important to have it with you at all times.
That way you can just flick to whatever page you need and be presented with a full
list of different things to do. That way you're never going to run out of ideas.
With small penis humiliation clients, I would recommend just really
going for it. They're there for the reason.
They want to be humiliated for the size of their penis.
A lot of times they'll show you it, but sometimes they may even show you it, and
it's not even small. It's like a normal average size, or sometimes it could even
be quite big. But for some reason, they want to be humiliated as if it's small.
So just bear that in mind when you have these types of clients.
Good luck girlies, and I'll see you again soon.